Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Verso: Where the Revolutionary War began, April 19, 1775 - the town common, Lexington, Mass.: At midnight on April 18, 1775, General Gage sent Lieutenant Colonel Smith, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50-verso (Box 1605)
  - Sacred to the cause of American Liberty - Bunker Hill Monument, Boston, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Sacred to the cause of American Liberty - Bunker Hill Monument, Boston, Mass.: It was on this hill, June 15th, 1775, that the famous battle was fought between the American Patriots and British troops, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Constitution, most famous of American warships, Boston Navy Yard, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Constitution, most famous of American warships, Boston Navy Yard, Mass.: In July, 1812, shortly after the outbreak of the second war with Great Britain, the United States ship Constitution, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52-verso (Box 1605)
  - Historic center of stirring revolutionary scenes - Old State House from Court Street, Boston, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Historic center of stirring revolutionary scenes - Old State House from Court Street, Boston, Mass.: This is one of the few colonial buildings surviving in Boston, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53-verso (Box 1605)
  - Fishing boat unloading halibut at dock, Boston Fish Pier, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Fishing boat unloading halibut at dock, Boston Fish Pier, Mass.: In nearly every country of the world the fishing industry is of importance, furnishing a large part of their food supplies to peoples living near sea coasts, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Old North Church, Boston, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Old North Church, Boston, Mass.: It was from the belfry tower of this old North Church that the signal lanterns were hung for Paul Revere, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55-verso (Box 1605)
  - Quincy Market and Fanuell Hall, Boston, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Quincy Market and Fanuell Hall, Boston, Mass.: Faneuil Hall, often called "The Cradle of Liberty," stands in the center of the business section of Boston, Massachusetts, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56-verso (Box 1605)
  - Boston, Mass., from an airplane, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Boston, Mass., from an airplane: About the beautiful city which we see spread far below us cluster probably more stirring memores of colonial and revolutionary history, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57-verso (Box 1605)
  - Slater Mill, first cotton mill in United States, Pawtuckett, R.I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Slater Mill, first cotton mill in United States, Pawtuckett, R.I.: The early American colonists bought all the cotton cloth they used from England, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58-verso (Box 1605)
  - The famous Yale Bowl, during a football game, New Haven, Conn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The famous Yale Bowl, during a football game, New Haven, Conn.: We are gazing at a spectacle which, through association of ideas, carries us back in spirit, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59-verso (Box 1605)
  - Spinning silk - showing roving frame, So. Manchester, Conn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Spinning silk - showing roving frame, So. Manchester, Conn.: This is a long spinning frame in a silk mill, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60-verso (Box 1605)
  - First drawing or straightening of fibers - silk industry (spun silk), So. Manchester, Conn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: First drawing or straightening of fibers - silk industry (spun silk), So. Manchester, Conn.: A great deal of the raw silk we get does not come to us in skeins, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61-verso (Box 1605)
  - General view of stitching and fitting department in a large shoe factory, Syracuse, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: General view of stitching and fitting department in a large shoe factory, Syracuse, N.Y.: Your shoes are made up of two parts, the soles and the uppers, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62-verso (Box 1605)
  - Summer spraying in apple orchard, Hilton, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Summer spraying in apple orchard, Hilton, N.Y.: Just as the rose is spoken of as the "Queen of the Garden," the apple is thought of as the "King of the Orchard", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63-verso (Box 1605)
  - The winter glory of the American Falls, Niagara Falls, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The winter glory of the American Falls, Niagara Falls, N.Y.: Rarely does tremendous power clothe itself with such beauty of form as it does in these wonderful falls of the Niagara, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64-verso (Box 1605)
  - Niagara from Prospect Point, looking toward Horseshoe or Canadian Falls, Niagara Falls, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Niagara from Prospect Point, looking toward Horseshoe or Canadian Falls, Niagara Falls, N.Y.: The Niagara River is so called from the Iroquois "Jarakare," meaning "thundering water", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65-verso (Box 1605)
  - Looking S.W. from Lafayette Theater building across Lafayette Square, Buffalo, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Looking S.W. from Lafayette Theater building across Lafayette Square, Buffalo, N.Y.: Lafayette Square lies in the heart of the downtown section of Buffalo, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66-verso (Box 1605)
  - Automatic machine for filling and capping bottles of milk, Cohocton, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Automatic machine for filling and capping bottles of milk, Cohocton, N.Y.: From the great dairy farms milk is generally whipped to cities in cans, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67-verso (Box 1605)
  - The hydraulic laborotory and Beebe Lake, school of engineering, Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The hydraulic laborotory and Beebe Lake, school of engineering, Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.: There is a growing tendency for the engineer to take a leading place in industrial administration, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68-verso (Box 1605)
  - Weaving room in the famous silk mills at Paterson, N.J., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Weaving room in the famous silk mills at Paterson, N.J.: After the silken threads from the cocoons are spun into yarn, they may vbe dyed or used plain., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69-verso (Box 1605)
  - Electric motor hauling cars loaded with coal to foot of shaft, near Scranton, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Electric motor hauling cars loaded with coal to foot of shaft, near Scranton, Penn.: Here you are at the bottom of an anthracite, or, hard coal mine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70-verso (Box 1605)
  - From corner of Commerce and Broad Sts., Newark, N.J., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: From corner of Commerce and Broad Sts., Newark, N.J.: Not every great city is fortunate enough to have been so designed as to possess beauty as well as industrial importance, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71-verso (Box 1605)
  - Milking scene in Modern Dairy, New Jersey, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Milking scene in Modern Dairy, New Jersey: The dairy industry in our country is relatively young, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72-verso (Box 1605)
  - General view of decorating shop in a large pottery plant, Trenton, N.J., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: General view of decorating shop in a large pottery plant, Trenton, N.J.: There is nothing more beautiful than an artistic piece of pottery, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73-verso (Box 1605)
  - Looking north on Broad St., City Hall in distance, Philadelphia, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Looking north on Broad St., City Hall in distance, Philadelphia, Penn.: No American city can compare with Philadelphia in historic interest nor the possession of treasures of olden times, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74-verso (Box 1605)
  - Memorial Hall, Pennsylvania Museum and school of Industrial Art, Philadelphia, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Memorial Hall, Pennsylvania Museum and school of Industrial Art, Philadelphia, Penn.: The Philadelphia Museum of Art is an important reproduction of the Greek Temples of the fourth qand fifth centuries, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Old Liberty Bell, Independence Hall, Philadelphia, Pa., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Old Liberty Bell, Independence Hall, Philadelphia, Pa.: In Independence Hall in Philadelphia there are many interesting relics, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76-verso (Box 1605)
  - Independence Hall, where the Declaration of Independence was signed in 1776, Philadelphia, Pa., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Independence Hall, where the Declaration of Independence was signed in 1776, Philadelphia, Pa.: The hall may be justly called one of the cradles of American liberty, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77-verso (Box 1605)
  - Stripping coal at Hazelton, Pa., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Stripping coal at Hazelton, Pa.: When a vein of coal lies near the surface of the Earth it is mined in the way shown in this picture, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78-verso (Box 1605)
  - Miner and laborer at work in Anthracite Coal Mine, near Scranton, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Miner and laborer at work in Anthracite Coal Mine, near Scranton, Penn.: We see here a miner and his helper working in a coal mine far beneath the surface of the ground, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79-verso (Box 1605)
  - Planting trout in a trout stream, Wayne County, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Planting trout in a trout stream, Wayne County, Penn.: Most men who live in the cities now have a day and a half of vacation at the end of the week, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80-verso (Box 1605)
  - Shooting an oil well with nitro-glycerin, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Shooting an oil well with nitro-glycerin, Penn.: The word petroleum means "rock oil" or oil that comes from the ground, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81-verso (Box 1605)
  - Steel Ingot on the "Table" of the "Blooming" Mill, Pittsburgh, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Steel Ingot on the "Table" of the "Blooming" Mill, Pittsburgh, Penn.: After the iron has been melted in the blast furnace and carbon has been driven into it, it is tested, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82-verso (Box 1605)
  - Filling molds with steel, Pittsburgh, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Filling molds with steel, Pittsburgh, Penn.: Steel is refined iron, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83-verso (Box 1605)
  - Modern pig iron machine at rest, Pittsburgh, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Modern pig iron machine at rest, Pittsburgh, Penn.: You see here the finishing operation in the making of pig iron by the latest method, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84-verso (Box 1605)
  - Blast furnace plant, Pittsburgh, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Blast furnace plant, Pittsburgh, Penn.: The United States leads all other countries in the production of iron ore and in the manufacturing of iron and steel, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85-verso (Box 1605)
  - Junction of the Allegheny and Monogahela Rivers. Pittsburgh, Pa., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Junction of the Allegheny and Monogahela Rivers. Pittsburgh, Pa.: The Allegheny and Monogahela Rivers unite to form the Ohio where Pittsburgh is now located, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86-verso (Box 1605)
  - General view of Coke Ovens - loading coke into the cars, Connellsville, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: General view of Coke Ovens - loading coke into the cars, Connellsville, Penn.: If you have ever seen bituminous or soft coal burn in a furnace or stove, you know that it produces a great deal of smoke, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87-verso (Box 1605)
  - Rounding the famous horseshoe curve. Allegheny Mountains, in Pennsylvania., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Rounding the famous horseshoe curve. Allegheny Mountains, in Pennsylvania.: This scene is justly famous by virtue of the work of both man and nature, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88-verso (Box 1605)
  - Looking S.E. across the Devil's Den, scene of one of America's fiercest battles, Gettysburg, Penn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Looking S.E. across the Devil's Den, scene of one of America's fiercest battles, Gettysburg, Penn.: No American battlefield ever witnessed a more sanguinary struggle than occurred on this boulder-strewn hill, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89-verso (Box 1605)
  - Picking peaches, Delaware, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Picking peaches, Delaware: Here you are shown a part of an industry that has developed fairly recently, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90-verso (Box 1605)
  - Gigantic wye oak, near Wye mills on the Eastern shore of Maryland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Gigantic wye oak, near Wye mills on the Eastern shore of Maryland: The "Wye oak"is one of the locally famous landmarks of that peaceful and fertile region of Maryland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91-verso (Box 1605)
  - On the deck of an Oyster Boat, Chesapeake Bay, Md., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: On the deck of an Oyster Boat, Chesapeake Bay, Md.: This view shows thousands of oysters which have been pulled in by means of dredges which scrape the oysters from the ocean bottom into the nets, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92-verso (Box 1605)
  - Bancroft Hall, United States Naval Academy, Annapolis Md., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Bancroft Hall, United States Naval Academy, Annapolis Md.: In the earlier years of the American republic, young men who wished to become officers in the United States Navy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93-verso (Box 1605)
  - The President of the United States and his cabinet, Washington, D.C., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The president of the United States and his cabinet, Washington, D.C.: Descending from our point of vantage in the State, War and Navy building, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94-verso (Box 1605)
  - White House (North Front), the historic official home of the President, Washington, D.C., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: White House (North Front), the historic official home of the President, Washington, D.C.: With the exception of the Capitol itself, the beautiful building before us is the oldest structure in Washington devoted to public uses, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95-verso (Box 1605)
  - Washington Monument - a towering memorial in an exquisite setting. Washington, D.C., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Washington Monument - a towering memorial in an exquisite setting. Washington, D.C.: Liong before his train enters the city of Washington, the white shaft of this beautiful monument catches the traveler's eyes, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96-verso (Box 1605)
  - Decorative splendor of the entrance hall,Congressional Library, Washington, D.C., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Decorative splendor of the entrance hall,Congressional Library, Washington, D.C.: This is one of the noblest entrance halls ever designed, a veritable vision in polished stone, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97-verso (Box 1605)
  - The dazzling dome of the Capitol on a rainy night, Washington D.C., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The dazzling dome of the Capitol on a rainy night, Washington D.C.: Whether seen by day, when it rises into the sky like a dazzling cloud, or by night when thrown into brilliant relief, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98-verso (Box 1605)
  - The nation's pride - Washington, Capital City of the United States, from an airplane., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The nation's pride - Washington, Capital City of the United States, from an airplane.: We are looking upon the seat of government of a mighty nation, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99-verso (Box 1605)
  - Our ambassador of the air - Col. Lindbergh and plane Spirit of St. Louis, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Our ambassador of the air - Col. Lindbergh and plane Spirit of St. Louis: When on May 21, 1927, Charles A. Lindbergh, a virtually unknown United States air mail pilot, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100-verso (Box 1605)
  Box 1606
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Coffee pickers at work, plantation scene in Guadaloupe, French West Indies, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Coffee pickers at work, plantation scene in Guadaloupe, French West Indies: The coffee plant is an evergreen shrub which may grow as high as twenty feet, but is seldom allowed to become more than six or eight feet in height, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1-verso (Box 1606)
  - Mighty earthquake fissure - "Lac du Nord." Soufriere Volcano, Guadaloupe, French West Indies, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Mighty earthquake fissure - "Lac du Nord." Soufriere Volcano, Guadaloupe, French West Indies: In the light of twentieth century values it seems strange enough to think that England's joy at the Naval victory, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Sponge fleet, Nassau, Bahama Islands, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Sponge fleet, Nassau, Bahama Islands: Before us lies at anchor the sponge fleet of Nassau, a forest of masts, a jumble of sails and rigging, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3-verso (Box 1606)
  - Eskimos with summer tents, Greenland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Eskimos with summer tents, Greenland: This is one of the most northerly points where any human beings live, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4-verso (Box 1606)
  - An eskimo family at Fort Magnesia, Cape Sabine, Ellsmere Land, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: An eskimo family at Fort Magnesia, Cape Sabine, Ellsmere Land: We are at Fort Magnesia on Cape Sabine, projecting from the extreme eastern coast of Ellesmere Land, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5-verso (Box 1606)
  - Whalers cruising in the Arctic - Dexterity Harbor and Bafflin Land, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Whalers cruising in the Arctic - Dexterity Harbor and Bafflin Land: These two boats cruising about in the ice-locked waters of Dexterity Harbor, off Baffin Land, are the "Diana" and the "Nova Zembla", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6-verso (Box 1606)
  - Spreading codfish to dry at Battle Harbor, Labrador, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Spreading codfish to dry at Battle Harbor, Labrador: When the boats come in, the fish are sorted and those required for the fresh fish trade, after being dressed, go to the refrigerator cars and to market, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7-verso (Box 1606)
  - Eskimo dog team on trail, Hopedale, Labrador, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Eskimo dog team on trail, Hopedale, Labrador: Labrador lies on the northeast coast of North America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8-verso (Box 1606)
  - A fishing village near St. John's Newfoundland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: A fishing village near St. John's Newfoundland: In the Gulf of Saint Lawrence lies the rugged island of Newfoundland..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9-verso (Box 1606)
  - "In the Acadian Land," on the shores of the Basine of Minas, Nova Scotia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: "In the Acadian Land," on the shores of the Basine of Minas, Nova Scotia: Distant, secluded, still, the little village of Grand-pre lay in the fruitful valley, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10-verso (Box 1606)
  - Ouiatchouan Falls, near Lake St. John, Quebec, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Ouiatchouan Falls, near Lake St. John, Quebec, Canada: The Ouiatchouan River runs its short turbulent course northward into Lake St. John, its source being the Lac de Commissaires, a few miles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Land of the Habitant, near Quebec, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Land of the Habitant, near Quebec, Canada: The first white settlers along the St. Lawrence river were French gentlemen, called "seigneurs", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12-verso (Box 1606)
  - "The most picturesque city in North America" - Quebec from the Citadel, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: "The most picturesque city in North America" - Quebec from the Citadel, Canada: We are facing about north and looking along the old ramparts of Dufferin Terrace, the famous promenade extending from the Citadel, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13-verso (Box 1606)
  - Beet pulp and juice flowing from tank to tank, Montreal, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Beet pulp and juice flowing from tank to tank, Montreal, Canada: A great deal of the juice flows from the beets into the slicing machine, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Wharves, Montreal, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Wharves, Montreal, Canada: Montreal is the great commercial center of the Dominion of Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15-verso (Box 1606)
  - Among the Iroquois Indians, Province of Quebec, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Among the Iroquois Indians, Province of Quebec, Canada: There were two main stocks of Indians that figured in the early history of Canada, the Algonquins and the Iroquois, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16-verso (Box 1606)
  - Bridge across Ottawa River and Dominion Government buildings, Ottawa, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Bridge across Ottawa River and Dominion Government buildings, Ottawa, Canada: From the low ground on the north bank of the Ottawa river, looking beneath the spans of this great bridge, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17-verso (Box 1606)
  - 19,000 cords of pulpwood at Fort William, Ontario, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: 19,000 cords of pulpwood at Fort William, Ontario: Up on the north shore of Lake Superior is Fort William - one of the busiest cities in Ontario, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18-verso (Box 1606)
  - Banff Springs Hotel, Canadian Rockies, Alberta Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Banff Springs Hotel, Canadian Rockies, Alberta Canada: With the continually increasing use of automobiles for touring, larger numbers of people, both from Canada itself and from the United States, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19-verso (Box 1606)
  - Lake Louise, "The Queen of Lakes," and Mount Victoria, Canadian Rockies, Alberta, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Lake Louise, "The Queen of Lakes," and Mount Victoria, Canadian Rockies, Alberta, Canada: The province of Alberta is directly east of British Columbia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20-verso (Box 1606)
  - Mount Sir Donald, the Matterhorn of the North American "Alps," British Columbia, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Mount Sir Donald, the Matterhorn of the North American "Alps," British Columbia, Canada: The grandest mountain scenery in North America is in the northern Cordillera from Wyoming to Alaska, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21-verso (Box 1606)
  - A treacherous crevasse in Victoria Glacier, Mt. Lefroy and Mt. Victoria in distance, Canadian Rockies, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22 (Box 1606)